<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction on REG Handbook</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction on REG Handbook</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Discussions and Issues</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/contributing/discussions_and_issues/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/contributing/discussions_and_issues/</guid><description>Discussions and Issues # Contributing does not only mean adding code or writing pages. Being involved in reporting issues and discussing ideas are important and valuable aspects to contributing. The handbook uses both issues and discussions on GitHub.
Discussions # The handbook Dicussions are the best place for informal talk about the handbook.
You should feel welcome to create a discussion on any relevant topic, without the formality of an issue.</description></item><item><title>Buddy System</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/onboarding/buddy_system/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/onboarding/buddy_system/</guid><description>Buddy System # It can be daunting starting a new job, especially remotely where there is sometimes less opportunity for casual questions. To help with this every new employee should be assigned buddies. The buddies are responsible for providing informal friendly faces to offer advice, guidance, and encouragement on any aspect of working within REG and ARC.
We also emphasise that the buddies should be a safe space where new-starters can get help with any technical questions that they feel is silly or trivially easy and may not feel comfortable admitting to the wider group.</description></item><item><title>Coffee Chats</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/regular_events/coffee_chats/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/regular_events/coffee_chats/</guid><description>Coffee Chats # The team has two optional, daily coffee chats at 08:45 and 13:45. The chats usually happen in Gather but there is also a Zoom room in case Gather is unavailable. Details for both rooms can be found here.</description></item><item><title>Drop-in Sessions</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/regular_events/drop-in_sessions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/regular_events/drop-in_sessions/</guid><description>Drop-in Sessions # The group runs regular, informal, community-led sessions for students and researchers. At the sessions they can ask the group about specific technical problems, or seek general technical advice. The sessions offer a friendly, welcoming, non-judgemental environment to receive advice or assistance without concern about being judged on technical knowledge, expertise or understanding.
As our organisers and helpers know, many of us working with software in the research community have been trained in domains where computing has not traditionally been a key element.</description></item><item><title>First Few Days</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/onboarding/new_joiners/first_few_days/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/onboarding/new_joiners/first_few_days/</guid><description>First Few Days # Welcome!
We are super pleased that you&amp;rsquo;re joining our group. This page gives you an overview of what to expect from your first few days. They are maintained by the group, we hope that new-starters feel empowered to edit them if there are useful changes to be made.
Introductions # Each new starter gets assigned two buddies to be friendly points of contact. Your line manager should let you know who these are.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/contributing/getting_started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/contributing/getting_started/</guid><description>Getting Started # Install dependencies # To contribute to the handbook you will need
Git Hugo (You will need the extended version with Sass/SCSS support) Your favourite text editor You might also find it helpful to install markdownlint so that you can lint your branch before making a pull request.
The linting style used is included in the root of the repository, .mdl_style.rb.
Clone the repository # Clone the repository with one of the following options (depending on how you authenticate with GitHub):</description></item><item><title>Knowledge Sharing</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/how_we_work/knowledge_sharing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/how_we_work/knowledge_sharing/</guid><description>Knowledge Sharing # This page lists the tools, resources and activities that REG has to promote general communication as well as sharing and gaining knowledge across the team (and the Turing as a whole), and some thoughts on what we could try to improve this. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to learn something new, get help with a problem, share something cool you&amp;rsquo;ve been doing, or find out what others in the team are doing, the list below may give an idea of where to look/what to try.</description></item><item><title>Lightning Talks</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/regular_events/lightning_talks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/regular_events/lightning_talks/</guid><description>Lightning Talks # Lightning Talks are a meeting series within the tech talk slots in which people give short 10 minute talks. The main goals are to:
Regularly share what we&amp;rsquo;re working on. Find overlaps between projects or problems someone else in the team could help with. Generate ideas for future tech talks. Do all this without a big time commitment, both for presenters and attendees. The talks can be on any topic, including but not limited to:</description></item><item><title>Lunchtime Tech Talks</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/regular_events/lunchtime_tech_talks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/regular_events/lunchtime_tech_talks/</guid><description>Lunchtime Tech Talks # The Research Engineering team meets for Lunchtime Tech Talks most Tuesdays over lunch. The talks start at 12:30.
The Data Science Skills wiki contains the talks schedule, calendar invitation instructions and information on signing up for a talk.</description></item><item><title>Reading Groups</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/regular_events/reading_groups/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/regular_events/reading_groups/</guid><description>Reading Groups # A list of current reading groups and information about them can be found on the Data Science Skills wiki.
Material for the reading groups is stored in the Data Science Skills repository</description></item><item><title>Twitter</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/communications/twitter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/communications/twitter/</guid><description>Twitter # The group has a Twitter account @turinghut23. The purpose of the account is to have an informal public-facing channel where we can communicate about projects we are working on and about life as a research engineer at the Turing.
Access # If you want to tweet under the group account, ask the account controller for access.
This also gives you access to Medium
What to Post # Projects we work on (if public) Blog posts Talks that we organise Conferences and workshops Any public outputs — papers, published code etc.</description></item><item><title>Changelogs and Semantic Versioning</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/technical_practices/change_logs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/technical_practices/change_logs/</guid><description>Changelogs # For any non-trivial code, it is worth maintaining a Changelog. This is valuable as it is a record of changes from the perspective of users (rather than git commit messages which are often only meaningful to the developers involved). A recommended format for Changelog files is given at Keep a changelog. All notable changes to a project should be documented in this file.
Semantic Versioning # A related concept is semantic versioning.</description></item><item><title>Meeting Records</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/how_we_work/meeting_record/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/how_we_work/meeting_record/</guid><description>Meeting Records # When a synchronous meeting is unavoidable, it is critical to produce a clear and thorough record.
The meeting record is important as a reference for what happened at the meeting. In particular, any decisions made or actions assigned need to be clearly recorded for future reference.
A good record will also be invaluable to anyone who was not able to attend an in person meeting.
Meeting Record Template # Below is a suggested template for a meeting record document.</description></item><item><title>Repo Audits</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/how_we_work/code_audits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/how_we_work/code_audits/</guid><description>Repo Audits # As required we conduct audits of GitHub repositories created during projects. The aim is to check that the documentation is clear, installation is easy etc.
Audits should be conducted by people who have not worked on the project.
Past experience # These comments from running the first round of these in June 2021:
Installation is a big barrier for software with complex build requirements. We tried looking at two web app projects (Counterfactual Covid 19 and CROP) and despite Docker images being available we weren&amp;rsquo;t able to get them to build correctly.</description></item><item><title>Style Guide</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/contributing/style_guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/contributing/style_guide/</guid><description>Style Guide # Semantic Line Breaks # It is encouraged to use Semantic Line Breaks when writing for the handbook. This improves the readability of source files and make diffs clearer. The Semantic Line Breaks specification explains the rules and reasoning. The most important rules are,
A semantic line break MUST occur after a sentence, as punctuated by a period (.), exclamation mark (!), or question mark (?). A semantic line break SHOULD occur after an independent clause as punctuated by a comma (,), semicolon (;), colon (:), or em dash (—).</description></item><item><title>Adding New Content</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/contributing/creating_a_page/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/contributing/creating_a_page/</guid><description>Adding New Content # How Hugo Arranges Content # Pages are build from content files in the content/ directory. Hugo automatically gives pages a URL based on the organisation of files in the content/ directory.
In Hugo, the first directory after content/ is significant and defines the content type. All handbook pages should be nested in the content/docs/ directory.
Sections may be created in content/docs/ (to any depth) by creating a directory containing a content file called _index.</description></item><item><title>Project Tracking</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/our_projects/project_tracking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/our_projects/project_tracking/</guid><description>Project Tracking # This page describes some of the tools we use for tracking projects and other tasks within the team.
Hut23 GitHub Repo # The Hut23 repo is the central hub for most team matters and admin.
Project Tracker: Board shows all upcoming, current and completed projects. There&amp;rsquo;s an issue for each project (see below). Issues: Each project has an issue following a common template, including a general description of a project and its current status, for example.</description></item><item><title>Python Tools and Practices</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/technical_practices/python/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/technical_practices/python/</guid><description>Python Tools and Practices # Python is a widely used language within REG. Below are some useful tools to help you configure your repo (with links to examples).
Some of the topics discussed below are not exclusive to Python. As more content is added to the manual they should be separated out into their own pages. Autoformatters / Linters # There are many widely used autoformatter and linters for Python, which can be used as standalone tools or call from .</description></item><item><title>Systems Set Up</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/onboarding/new_joiners/systems_set_up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/onboarding/new_joiners/systems_set_up/</guid><description>Systems Set Up # These are not hand-holding instructions. Rather they are a reference to help with your setup. If they are wrong or incomplete, please edit them. The page has been roughly organised high priority things (do in your first couple of days), low priority (sometimes in the first couple of weeks), and reference.
If any of the material is unfamiliar (e.g. you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen a GitHub project board before), then please ask your buddies (or anyone else you meet in the group) to have an informal chat about it.</description></item><item><title>Configuring Your Editor</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/technical_practices/configuring_editors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/technical_practices/configuring_editors/</guid><description>Configuring Your Editor # Many people will configure their editor to suit their own needs and preferences.
It is possible to do this so that there are common standards between collaborators in the code base, while allowing for differences in individuals&amp;rsquo; configurations.
Some of the topics discussed below are heavily focused on python development. In due course we should generalise this to cover other languages. General # Some common, particular formatting/encoding options can be configured for a range of editors/IDEs by using EditorConfig in your repo.</description></item><item><title>Editing a Page</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/contributing/editing_a_page/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/contributing/editing_a_page/</guid><description>Editing a Page # If you followed the instructions in the Getting Started section to checkout the repository and serve the handbook locally you can edit a page locally. However, as you may have noticed, at the bottom of each page is a link to edit the page in the GitHub web editor if you would prefer. This may be easy for making small changes.
Pages # Each page is a Markdown file with YAML front matter followed by the page contents in Markdown.</description></item><item><title>Contributing Changes</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/contributing/contributing_changes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/contributing/contributing_changes/</guid><description>Contributing Changes # Once you have made changes, you will need to contribute them back to the remote repository. This page explains the process of pushing your changes back to the remote, and how your contribution will be checked in the CI and review process.
Currently, reviews are not required. Pull requests may be merged by anyone with write access when all required CI checks pass.
You may enable auto-merge on a pull request so that a merge is made as soon as all checks pass.</description></item><item><title>Reviewing Changes</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/contributing/reviewing_changes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/contributing/reviewing_changes/</guid><description>Reviewing Changes # The review process helps to ensure high quality and catch problems in contributions. When acting as a reviewer, you should see your position as sharing your knowledge and working with the contributors to achieve the best possible result. Reviewing should not be an adversarial process.
Code Quality # As a reviewer, one of your jobs is to ensure the quality of the codebase remains high.
The CI process will help to assess pull requests by subjecting each commit to a series of tests.</description></item><item><title>Advanced</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/contributing/advanced/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/contributing/advanced/</guid><description>Advanced # Using Data # Through using templates Hugo can build page content from datafiles. This is particularly useful for when you want to display structured data in a page and when it would be easier to maintain a datafile rather than a Markdown or HTML document.
Creating Shortcodes # It is possible to create your own shortcodes. These should be placed in layouts/shortcodes/ .
If you feel the need to use HTML or want to create page content from a datafile (like a YAML file or csv) then a shortcode is probably the right answer.</description></item><item><title>Project Outputs</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/our_projects/project_outputs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/our_projects/project_outputs/</guid><description>Project Outputs # See this page</description></item></channel></rss>