<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Working at The Turing on REG Handbook</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/working_at_the_turing/</link><description>Recent content in Working at The Turing on REG Handbook</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/working_at_the_turing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Booking a Meeting Room</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/working_at_the_turing/booking_a_meeting_room/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/working_at_the_turing/booking_a_meeting_room/</guid><description>Booking a Meeting Room # There are instructions on how to book a room on Mathison.
The simplest way of finding a room is to use the Scheduling Assistant on a meeting invite.
Then scroll down to Add Location. This will give you a list of Available Rooms for your specific time. It will update when you move the time window.</description></item><item><title>Expenses</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/working_at_the_turing/expenses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/working_at_the_turing/expenses/</guid><description>Expenses # Out-of-pocket expenses # Out-of-pocket expenses should be reclaimed using Certify. You should submit an expense claim on Certify for expenses incurred within a given month as soon as possible, and no later than 60 days after the expense is incurred (except for visa costs, which can be claimed up to a year after starting employment).
In the first instance, look at the information provided by the Finance team about how to use Certify on Mathison:</description></item><item><title>Equality, Diversity, and Inclusion</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/working_at_the_turing/edi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/working_at_the_turing/edi/</guid><description>Equality, Diversity, and Inclusion # Overview # The Turing has a strong commitment towards EDI, which is formally set out in the Institute&amp;rsquo;s EDI Strategy and Action Plan. For current Turing staff, you can also access an EDI section on Mathison.
How to get involved # If you are keen to be involved in the EDI work around REG and the Turing, do feel free to join the #edi-equality-diversity-inclusion channel on Slack, and/or contact:</description></item><item><title>Reasonable Adjustments</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/working_at_the_turing/reasonable_adjustments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/working_at_the_turing/reasonable_adjustments/</guid><description>Reasonable Adjustments, Access to Work, and Office Accessibility # Reasonable Adjustments # Reasonable adjustments are changes to workplace procedures, practices, or environments that help ensure individuals with disabilities are not disadvantaged compared to others. These adjustments can address needs related to mental health, neurodiverse conditions, visual or hearing impairments, chronic illnesses, and mobility conditions.
Examples of reasonable adjustments which may be considered include:
Flexible working hours Workspace adjustments (e.g., footrests, back support, adjustable desks) Remote/hybrid working options Additional training Providing a mentor Assistive technology The Alan Turing Institute is committed to creating an inclusive, barrier-free workplace, recognising that providing reasonable adjustments is essential to supporting colleagues in fully participating in their roles.</description></item><item><title>Wellbeing</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/working_at_the_turing/wellbeing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/working_at_the_turing/wellbeing/</guid><description>Wellbeing # The Turing provides a number of support mechanisms to protect employees&amp;rsquo; wellbeing.
The most up-to-date information can be found on Mathison. A summary follows here:
Report + Support # Report + Support is an online platform where you can report cases of bullying, harassment, discrimination, assault, hate crime, sexual misconduct, or a breach of the Turing&amp;rsquo;s values (Trust, Inclusivity, Respect, Leadership, Transparency, Integrity). Reports can be made anonymously if you so choose.</description></item></channel></rss>