<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Employee processes on REG Handbook</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/employee_processes/</link><description>Recent content in Employee processes on REG Handbook</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/employee_processes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Probation</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/employee_processes/probation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/employee_processes/probation/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="probation"&gt;
 Probation
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#probation"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the initial 6 months in a team member&amp;rsquo;s appointment to the institute, they will undergo probation review with their line manager. (Note that if an existing team member was previously in another role at the Turing and underwent probation review in that role, they do not require a probation review when appointed to a role in REG.) This is designed to integrate with the on-boarding process to ensure that new team members are performing their job as expected. This wiki page outlines the expectations for team members and line managers in going through the probation process.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Annual Appraisals</title><link>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/employee_processes/annual_appraisals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alan-turing-institute.github.io/REG-handbook/docs/employee_processes/annual_appraisals/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="annual-appraisals"&gt;
 Annual Appraisals
 &lt;a class="anchor" href="#annual-appraisals"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;REG is a large team, with a relatively flat line management structure. Therefore we run a team-wide standardisation process where appraisals and progression award recommendations are reviewed to ensure consistency and fairness across the team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our goal is to work within the wider HR policy and guidance (see &lt;a href="https://mathison.turing.ac.uk/page/2319"&gt;HR Performance Review Guide&lt;/a&gt;) to prioritise what we think is most important for our team (fairness, transparency and a clear progression path) and provide clear guidance to achieve that.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>